Viewers, I know that you are here.
But you still want me to look at you, you alone.
I'm talking to you, listen to me.
Carry Heaven along.
Wherever you are, Heaven knows that you are there.
Heaven.
Our Father who art in Heaven, hallowed be thy name, thy Kingdom come, thy will be done.
When you carry Heaven along, you do the will of the Father.
I pray for enablement, in the name of Jesus!
Jesus knows what you are talking about.
You are talking about your weakness.
You are talking about your challenges.
You are talking about your situation.
Jesus knows what you are talking about.
That challenge does not mean that you are not a Christian.
That you have challenges does not mean that you are not a Christian.
Don't measure your Christian life by your challenges.
This is the situation with you.
Your heart, your spirit testifies
that you are a Christian.
The challenges you have are meant to promote you.
The challenges that you have
are meant for your spiritual benefit.
Receive in the name of Jesus!
Through that challenge, I can see the next promotion.
Pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name.
Desire to serve God!
Determination to serve God!
I can see you grow, in the name of Jesus!
Your challenge is meant to grow you, in the name of Jesus!
Don't listent to the voice of challenges.
Listen to God.
Challenges are meant to grow you in your Christian journey.
Look at what happened to Job.
Satan said to God, "Leave this man for me.
Let me give him challenges and situations".
The voice of challenges is to tell you,
"No, Jesus does not love me.
Jesus does not love me. I'm not faithful".
But no, listen to me!
I can see you growing, in the name of Jesus!
I can see you growing in your business!
That sickness be cursed, in the name of Jesus!
Wherever it is located in your system,
in your body, in your fluids, in your blood -
be cursed, in the name of Jesus!
Every spirit that torments your life,
every spirit that causes you sickness and disease,
every spirit that causes you disappointment,
every spirit that causes you nightmares,
be cursed, in the name of Jesus!
Heaven knows that you are there.
Confess this and begin to rebuke those spirits!
Curse them, in the name of Jesus!
Heaven knows you are here!
Thank You, Jesus!